Guide to the Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- 1980 Addition, 1957-1976; 1974-1976
  - Family correspondence and records
    - [Wilkie, Neil?], 1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - Williams, Faith (Morrow), 1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - Yates, Cynthia (Knoch), 1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - Yates, Edith, 1974, undated (Box 214, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence with publishers
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1974-1975, undated (Box 214, Folder 39)
    - Pantheon Books, 1974-1975 (Box 214, Folder 39)
    - Other publishers, 1974-1975, undated (Box 214, Folder 40-41)
  - General correspondence
    - 1962-1975 March (Box 214, Folder 42-45)
    - 1975 April-1976, undated (Box 215, Folder 46-49)
    - Condolences after Charles A. Lindbergh's death, 1974 August-November
      - A-B (Box 215, Folder 50-51)
      - C-H (Box 216, Folder 52-57)
      - I-O (Box 217, Folder 58-64)
      - P-Wh (Box 218, Folder 65-70)
      - Wi-Z, unidentified (Box 219, Folder 71-72)
      - Condolences from organizations (Box 219, Folder 73)
      - Condolences from cities, towns, and states (Box 219, Folder 74)
      - Condolences from celebrities (Box 219, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence from readers
    - "Prayer for Peace", 1974 (Box 219, Folder 76)
    - Gift from the Sea, 1974-1975 (Box 219, Folder 76)
    - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead, 1973-1975 (Box 219, Folder 77)
    - Locked Rooms and Open Doors, 1974-1975, undated (Box 219, Folder 78)
    - Reader comments on Anne Morrow Lindbergh's writing in general, 1973-1975 (Box 219, Folder 79)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1962-1976, undated (Box 219, Folder 80-83)
  - Writings
    - Lists and notes regarding copies of books sent by Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Undated (Box 220, Folder 84)
    - Notes and drawings (early) of grave at Kipahulu, Undated (Box 220, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous notes, Undated (Box 220, Folder 85)
    - Locked Rooms and Open Doors: reviews and notices, 1974 (Box 220, Folder 86)
  - Housekeeping and social records
    - Bills for Charles A. Lindbergh's hospitalization, 1974 (Box 220, Folder 87)
    - Bills for Maui, 1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 88)
    - Bills paid at Darien, 1974-1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 89-90)
    - Legal documents, 1957, 1970-1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 91)
  - Institutions, committees, and clubs
    - Chapin School Alumnae Association, 1974-1976 (Box 220, Folder 92)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 92)
    - Elisabeth Morrow School, 1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 92)
    - International Civil Aviation Organization: presentation of Edward Warner Award to Charles A. Lindbergh
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 93)
      - Anne Morrow Lindbergh's speech and notes, 1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 94)
      - Printed matter, 1975 (Box 220, Folder 95)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1974-1975 (Box 220, Folder 96)
    - Smith College, 1973-1975 (Box 220, Folder 96)
    - Miscellaneous membership cards, 1975, undated (Box 220, Folder 97)
  - Memorabilia
    - List of condolence letters received, 1974 (Box 221, Folder 98)
    - Articles and clippings regarding Charles A. Lindbergh's death, 1974 August-1975, undated (Box 221, Folder 99-100)
    - Articles and clippings regarding Jon Lindbergh, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1974 (Box 221, Folder 101)
- 1982 Addition, 1920s-1982; 1973-1982
  The addition is arranged in ten sections: Correspondence from friends and acquaintances; Family correspondence and records; Correspondence with publishers; General correspondence; Correspondence with readers; Outgoing correspondence; Writings; Housekeeping and social records; Institutions, committees, and clubs; and Memorabilia.
  Headings in the addition correspond to series titles in the main accession. The addition contains some material concerning the death of Charles Augustus Lindbergh in 1974, but most of the papers reflect Anne Morrow Lindbergh's activities from 1976 to 1981, including her involvement with a variety of ceremonies commemorating the fiftieth anniversary of her husband's 1927 flight. Incoming correspondence is often annotated. Usually, annotations on general correspondence were made by the secretary, while annotations on personal correspondence were made by Lindbergh. Their abbreviations include "RA" and "RU," for "requests answered" and "requests unanswered," and "LVM" for "lost in volume of mail" (and therefore not answered). Not all drafts and carbons of outgoing correspondence are found under that heading. Some are filed with the letters to which they respond under Correspondence with readers. Materials related to fiftieth anniversary activities are found with the Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund under Institutions, committees, and clubs.
  - Correspondence from friends and acquaintances
    - Allen, Helen, 1974 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Ames, Evelyn and Amyas, 1973-1979 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong, Christa, 1974, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Atchley, Dana W., 1975 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Atchley, Mary, 1976-1979 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Atchley, Sandol Stoddard, 1977-1978 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Atchley, William Ames, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Byard, Maggie, 1974 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle) and John, 1974-1979, undated (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Chilton, Constance, 1978 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Cole, Wayne S., 1977 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Crépin, Jean M., 1974 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Curtiss, Mina (Kirstein), 1974-1979 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Damon, Jean (Shields), 1974 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Wellesley Parson, 1976, 1978 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - DeCoux, Janet, 1973-1979 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Delafield, Mary (Walker), 1974 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Delattre, Yvonne, 1974-1978 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Dent, Frederick B., 1974 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Edmundson, D'arcy, 1973 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Eisenhower, Julie (Nixon), 1974-1979, undated (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Franklin, Helena and George, 1974-1979 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Frautschi, Judith (Guild), 1974 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Gloor, Gertrud, 1974 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Harris, Louisa, 1974-1979 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Hatt, Sue (Vaillant) and Robert T., [1974?]-1979 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Huber, Jack, 1974-1978 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Hunter-Gray, Nancy (de Selincourt), 1974-1979 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Kennan, George, 1974, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1974, 1978 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Knollenberg, Mary T., 1977, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Lamont, Corliss, 1973-1979 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Thelma, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Lescaze, Mary, 1974, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, Dorothy ("Dotsey"), [1974?]-1979 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Lyden, Ruth (Stephens), 1974 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - McCandless, Ruth, 1970-1971 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - McCloy, John J., 1974, 1977 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - McGavin, Ann, 1974, 1977-1979 (Box 222, Folder 13-14)
    - McLaughlin, Jeanne Biltz, 1974 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Matthias, Blanche, 1974-1977 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Moreillon, Eglantine and Henri, 1967, 1974-1979 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Moreillon, Jacques, 1974, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Munroe, Vernon, Jr. and Ofelia, 1974-1978 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Newton, James Draper and Eleanor (Forde), 1973-1976 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Newton, James Draper and Eleanor (Forde), 1977-1979 (Box 223, Folder 17)
      See also: Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund, boxes 243-246, folders 244-279
    - Obermer, Nesta, 1974-1979 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Oldrin, John, 1976, 1979 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Owen, John, 1973-1976 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Pryor, Mary Tay, [1972?]-1978 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Pryor, Samuel F., [1973?]-1977 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Read, David Thurber, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Regina Laudis Monastery, 1974-1979 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Robb, Lynda (Johnson), 1978-1979 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Rockefeller, Blanchette, 1978 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Rodewald, Elizabeth (Bacon), 1973-1977 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Romney, Katrina, 1974-1978 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Rosen, Hazel, 1973-1976 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Nancy Wilson, 1974, 1979 (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Saunders, Jean, 1974-1979 (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Sevareid, Eric, 1975-1977 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Shannon, Mary, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Katherine, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Stevens, George, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Stevens, Laura (Brandt), 1973 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Stirling, Monica, 1973-1979 (Box 223, Folder 24-26)
    - Stuart, Barbara, 1974-1979 (Box 223, Folder 27)
    - Sturm, Marthe, 1974-1976 (Box 223, Folder 27)
      See also: Regina Laudis Monastery, box 223, folder 20
    - Swanson, Minnie, 1976-1979 (Box 223, Folder 27)
    - Taquey, Charles H., 1976-1977 (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - Taquey, Kitty (McVitty), 1947, 1974, 1977 (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - Thomas, Tay, 1978 (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - Trask, Elsie (Barber), [1974?]-1977 (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - Trippe, Betty, 1975-1979 (Box 223, Folder 29)
    - Trippe, Juan T., 1974, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 29)
    - Vaillant, George, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 29)
    - Valentine, Alan, 1974, 1976 (Box 223, Folder 29)
    - Valentine, Lucia (Norton), 1974-1979 (Box 223, Folder 30)
    - Webster, Jean, 1974-[1976-1977] (Box 223, Folder 30)
    - Wheeler, Elsie (Trask), 1973-1978 (Box 223, Folder 31)
    - Wolff, Helen, 1974-1978, undated (Box 223, Folder 31)
  - Family correspondence and records
    - Brown, Marjory W., 1976-1977 (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Feydy, Charles, 1979 (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Feydy, Hélène, 1975-1979 (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Fulenwider, Constance, 1973-1979, undated (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Kenney, Susan (McIlvaine), 1973-1979 (Box 224, Folder 33)
    - Leighton, Katherine (McIlvaine), 1973-1977 (Box 224, Folder 33)
    - Lindbergh, Alika, 1974, 1978 (Box 224, Folder 33)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1973-1979 (Box 224, Folder 34-37)
    - Lindbergh, Barbara (Robbins), 1972-1979 (Box 224, Folder 38-39)
    - Lindbergh, Erik, 1974 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Lindbergh, Kristina R., 1970, 1974-1978 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Lindbergh, Lars, 1970 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Lindbergh, Leif, 1970, 1974 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Lindbergh, Peter, 1969 (Box 224, Folder 40)
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, 1973-1979, undated (Box 224, Folder 41-43)
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow, 1973-1979 (Box 225, Folder 44)
    - Lindbergh, Susan (Miller), 1973 (Box 225, Folder 44)
    - Lindbergh, Susan (Miller), 1974, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 45)
    - Lindbergh, Wendy, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 46)
    - Miller, Tom, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 46)
    - Morgan, Aubrey Niel, 1976-1977 (Box 225, Folder 46)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1973-1979 (Box 225, Folder 47-50)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr., 1969-1974 (Box 225, Folder 51)
    - Morrow, Margot (Loines), 1969, 1974-1979 (Box 225, Folder 51)
    - Morrow, Nancy Lofton, 1973-1979 (Box 225, Folder 52-53)
    - Morrow, Stephen Dwight, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 54)
    - Scandrett, Mary (Landenberger), 1974, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 54)
    - Spaeth, Eva Lindbergh Christie, 1974-1979 (Box 225, Folder 54)
    - Vogel, Robert, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 55)
    - Voorhees, Frederic, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 55)
    - Wilkie, Edith, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 55)
    - Wilkie, John, 1976 (Box 225, Folder 55)
    - Williams, Faith (Morrow), 1974, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 55)
    - Yates, Edith (Cutter), 1968-1973 (Box 225, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence with publishers
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1976-1978 (Box 226, Folder 56)
    - Pantheon books, 1974-1981 (Box 226, Folder 56)
    - Other publishers, 1972-1981 (Box 226, Folder 57-60)
  - General correspondence
    - 1952-1962, 1971-1973 (Box 227, Folder 61-71)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 228, Folder 72-81)
    - 1974 (Box 229, Folder 82)
    - Condolences after Charles A. Lindbergh's death, 1974-1975 (Box 229, Folder 83-84)
    - 1975 (Box 229, Folder 85-86)
    - Requests answered, 1976 (Box 229, Folder 87-89)
    - Requests unanswered, 1976 (Box 229, Folder 90)
    - Requests unanswered, 1976 (Box 230, Folder 91)
    - 1976 (Box 230, Folder 92)
    - Requests answered, 1977 (Box 230, Folder 93-100)
    - Requests answered, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 101-102)
    - Requests unanswered, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 103-108)
    - 1977 (Box 231, Folder 109-110)
    - 1977 (Box 232, Folder 111-124)
    - 1977 (Box 233, Folder 125-129)
    - Requests answered, 1978 (Box 233, Folder 130-135)
    - Requests answered, 1978 (Box 234, Folder 136)
    - Requests unanswered, 1978 (Box 234, Folder 137-138)
    - 1978 (Box 234, Folder 139-147)
    - 1978 (Box 235, Folder 148-150)
    - Requests answered, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 151-154)
    - Requests unanswered, 1979 (Box 235, Folder 155-157)
    - 1979 (Box 235, Folder 158-160)
    - 1979 (Box 236, Folder 161-164)
    - Requests answered, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 165-170)
    - Requests unanswered, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 171-172)
    - Requests unanswered, 1980 (Box 237, Folder 173-174)
    - 1980 (Box 237, Folder 175-184)
    - 1980 (Box 238, Folder 185-187)
    - Requests unanswered, 1981 (Box 238, Folder 188-189)
    - 1981 (Box 238, Folder 190-194)
    - 1981, undated (Box 238, Folder 195)
  - Correspondence with readers
    - North to the Orient, 1972, 1978, 1980 (Box 239, Folder 196)
    - Listen! The Wind, 1976 (Box 239, Folder 196)
    - The Steep Ascent, 1980-1981 (Box 239, Folder 196)
    - Gift from the Sea, 1960, 1972-1981 (Box 239, Folder 197-200)
    - The Unicorn and Other Poems, 1972, 1980-1981 (Box 239, Folder 201)
    - Dearly Beloved, 1977-1978 (Box 239, Folder 201)
    - Middlebury commencement speech, [1978?] (Box 239, Folder 201)
    - "The Journey Not the Arrival", 1978-1979 (Box 239, Folder 201)
    - Bring Me a Unicorn, 1972-1973, 1977-1980 (Box 239, Folder 202)
    - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead, 1973-1981 (Box 239, Folder 203)
    - Locked Rooms and Open Doors, 1977, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 204)
    - The Flower and the Nettle, 1976-1981 (Box 239, Folder 205-207)
    - War Within and Without, 1980 (Box 239, Folder 208-209)
    - War Within and Without, 1980-1981 (Box 240, Folder 210-211)
    - Reader comments on Anne Morrow Lindbergh's writings in general, 1973-1981 (Box 240, Folder 212-219)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1968, 1972-1979 (Box 241, Folder 220-225)
  - Writings
    - Diaries and Letters, Volumes II-V, 1970-1973, undated (Box 242, Folder 226)
      Notes, drafts, transcripts of letters, memoranda
    - The Flower and the Nettle, 1975-1976 (Box 242, Folder 227)
      Lists of copies sent by Anne Morrow Lindbergh
    - Charles A. Lindbergh's burial and memorial service
      - Drafts, 1974 (Box 242, Folder 228-229)
      - Copies, 1974 (Box 242, Folder 230)
    - Notes on dreams, 1978 (Box 242, Folder 231)
    - Scrapbook of Gift from the Sea, 1955-1957 (Box 242, Folder 232)
      Reviews and notices
    - Earth Shine, 1971 (Box 242, Folder 233)
    - Gift from the Sea, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 233)
    - Autobiography of Values, 1978 (Box 242, Folder 233)
    - Hour of Gold, Hour of Land, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 233)
    - Locked Rooms and Open Doors, 1974-1975 (Box 242, Folder 234)
    - The Flower and the Nettle, 1976, undated (Box 242, Folder 235-236)
  - Housekeeping and social records
    - Housekeeping and miscellaneous notes, 1973-1979, undated (Box 242, Folder 237)
    - Legal documents, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 237)
    - Bank statements, 1975 (Box 242, Folder 238)
    - Bills and receipts, 1974-1977 (Box 242, Folder 238)
    - Business firms, 1972-1975 (Box 242, Folder 239)
      Correspondence
    - Contributions, 1971-1979 (Box 242, Folder 240-242)
  - Institutions, committees, and clubs
    - Asia Society, 1973-1978, undated (Box 243, Folder 243)
    - Aviation Hall of Fame, 1978-1979 (Box 243, Folder 243)
    - Chapin School Alumnae Association, 1972-1977 (Box 243, Folder 243)
    - Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund
      - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 243, Folder 244-254)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 255-258)
      - Memorandum, 1976-1977, undated (Box 244, Folder 259-260)
      - Brochure, 1976 Oct, undated (Box 244, Folder 261)
      - December 2 luncheon and Anne Morrow Lindbergh's speech, 1976 November-December (Box 244, Folder 262)
      - 50th anniversary (miscellaneous), 1977 April-May, undated (Box 244, Folder 263)
      - Anne Morrow Lindbergh's open letter on 50th anniversary, Undated (Box 244, Folder 264)
      - 50th anniversary "Spirit of St. Louis" dinners
        - General, 1977 March-Apr, undated (Box 244, Folder 265)
        - Atlanta, April 30, 1977 February-May, undated (Box 244, Folder 266)
        - Chicago, May 12, 1977 [May?]-Jun, undated (Box 244, Folder 266)
        - Philadelphia, May 13, 1977 March-April (Box 244, Folder 266)
        - Washington, DC, May 19, 1976 December-1977 Jun, undated (Box 245, Folder 267)
        - New York, May 20, 1977 April-Jun, undated (Box 245, Folder 268-269)
      - 50th anniversary
        - Yale University Library, May 5, 1977 January-Sep, undated (Box 245, Folder 270)
        - St. Louis, May 11-12, 1976 December-1978 Jan, undated (Box 245, Folder 271-272)
        - New York, May 20, 1977January-Dec, undated (Box 245, Folder 273)
          Luncheons, awards, etc.
        - Washington, DC, May 20, 1976 September-1977 April (Box 245, Folder 274)
          Library of Congress luncheon
        - Little Falls, Minnesota, May 22, 1976 November-1977 November, undated (Box 245, Folder 275)
        - Paris, Jun 3-4, 1977 February-June (Box 245, Folder 276)
        - Paris, Jun 3-4, 1977 July-Oct, undated (Box 246, Folder 277)
        - Lindbergh Awards Dinner, May 23, 1978 January-Nov, undated (Box 246, Folder 278)
        - Printed material, 1976-1977, undated (Box 246, Folder 279)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1977-1979 (Box 246, Folder 280)
    - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1972-1973 (Box 246, Folder 280)
    - Elisabeth Morrow School, 1971-1975 (Box 246, Folder 280)
    - Experimental Aircraft Association: Lindbergh Commemorative Tour, 1976-1980, undated (Box 246, Folder 281-283)
    - Missouri Historical Society, 1974-1975 (Box 246, Folder 284)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1972-1978 (Box 246, Folder 285)
    - National Audubon Society, 1973-1981, undated (Box 246, Folder 285)
    - P.E.N. American Center, 1978-1979, undated (Box 246, Folder 285)
    - Pen and Brush, 1977 (Box 246, Folder 285)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1972-1979 (Box 246, Folder 286)
    - Smith College, 1971-1973, 1977-1981, undated (Box 246, Folder 287-288)
    - World Federation of United Nations Associations, 1977-1979, undated (Box 246, Folder 289-290)
  - Memorabilia
    - Articles and clippings, 1977 (Box 247, Folder 291-292)
      Regarding 50th anniversary of Charles A. Lindbergh's flight
    - Medal for Christopher Award, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 293)
    - Sample medal from Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund, 1977 (Box 247, Folder 293)
    - Georgetown University, 1978 (Box 247, Folder 294)
      Program for Anne Morrow Lindbergh's honorary degree ceremony
    - Sheet music for song "Who's the Man?", 1927 (Box 247, Folder 295)
    - Scrapbook of clippings regarding Charles A. Lindbergh, 1920s-1930s (Box 247, Folder 296)
    - Articles and clippings regarding Charles A. Lindbergh, 1920s (Box 247, Folder 297)
    - Articles and clippings, 1968-1977 (Box 247, Folder 298)
      Regarding Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1975, 1979, undated (Box 247, Folder 298)
    - Articles and clippings, 1977 (Box 247, Folder 299)
    - Audio tape, "National Air and Space Museum" ABC-TV, [1977?], 1979 (Box 247, Folder 300)
    - Medal and case from Aviation Hall of Fame, 1979 (Box 247, Folder 301)
    - Certificate honoring women of Connecticut during United Nation's International Women's Year and Decade, 1976 (Box 248, Folder 302)
    - Citation awarded to Anne Morrow Lindbergh by Aviation Hall of Fame, 1979 (Box 248, Folder 302)
    - Poster and brochure regarding Bowlus Glider, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 303)
    - Poster and brochure for National Women's History Week, 1982 (Box 248, Folder 303)
    - Articles and clippings, 1977 (Box 248, Folder 304)
    - Book Award, National Council of Women of the United States, 1955 November 10 (Box 248, Folder 305)
    - Certificate, American Museum Natural History, Associate Benefactor, and print, 1934 January (Box 248, Folder 305)
    - "A Conversation with Anne Morrow Lindbergh" [commercially produced], 1977 (Box 248A)
      Videotape of Anne Morrow Lindbergh's CBS-TV interview with Eric Sevareid
      Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
      Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
- Additional material, Circa 1929-1988; 1970-1985; Accession 1987-M-003
  The accession primarily consists of correspondence with family, friends and acquaintances. The bulk of the correspondence is incoming with a few outgoing responses included.
  The accession is arranged in six sections: Correspondence from friends and acquaintances, Family correspondence, Holiday cards, General correspondence, Writings, and Miscellaneous.
  - Correspondence from friends and acquaintances
    - Ames, Evelyn, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Atchely, Mary, 1977 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Atchely, William, 1983 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bassage, Anne, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bassage, Rev. Harold, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bell, Judy, 1964, 1983 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bingham, Alfred, 1982-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bingham, June, 1982 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Borden, Louise, 1983 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Mackey, 1983 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bruggman, Mary, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Burnett, Carol, 1981 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Byard, Maggie, 1983 September 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Carleton, Margaret, 1981 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cary, Katherine, 1983 April 3-October (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Cary, Linn, 1983 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle), 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle) and John R., Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Chamberlain, John R., Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Christen, Eliette, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Connor, Phoebe, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Coolidge, Harold, 1984 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Curtiss, Mina (Kirstein), 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Davidoff, Dr. Ida, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Davies, Kath E., 1983 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Delattre, Yvonne, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - De Vogue, Nely, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dodson, Irene, 1983 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Douglas, Ray, 1982 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Driscoll, John, 1980 October 8, 1981 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Ducret-Cochard, B., 1981 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Eisenhower, Julie (Nixon), 1983 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Eissler, Dr. Ruth, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ferguson, Joanne, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Fischer, Inge, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Frautschi, Judith (Guild), 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Fredette, Ray, 1983 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 37)